<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>stanleynguyen on thecodecousins</title><link>/authors/stanleynguyen/</link><description>Recent content in stanleynguyen on thecodecousins</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 16:08:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/authors/stanleynguyen/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Building my Github Action to deliver doggoes to PRs</title><link>/posts/doggo-action/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 16:08:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/doggo-action/</guid><description>The long awaited GitHub Action feature is finally out of beta and ready to be present in every repositories. GitHub even organized a Hackathon through out March to encourage folks to create more awesome and useful actions. While browsing through the submissions, I found a cool GitHub Action that posts cat gifs on pull requests. Shout out to Ruairidh with his cool idea 👏👏👏.
It&amp;rsquo;ll only do justice to dogs if there&amp;rsquo;s an action that deliver them good boys to our PRs.</description></item><item><title>Quick terminal-based DNS switching</title><link>/posts/dns-command/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2019 14:53:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/dns-command/</guid><description>Motivation Most of us, at some point of our lives, have used at least a custom DNS servers configurations for our computers. Be it for avoiding censorship, faster browsing, security, or bypassing content restriction, we&amp;rsquo;ve all tried setting our DNS servers to some public DNS servers like one from Google (remember 8.8.8.8 and 8.8.4.4?). I myself is also no exception as I have been using 1.1.1.1 for privacy and speed.</description></item><item><title>Example Blog Post</title><link>/posts/example/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 14:15:59 -0600</pubDate><guid>/posts/example/</guid><description>Section 1 This is some example content
Sub section 1 This is some content for subsection 1
Test Code highlight Go code with hugo highlight template
a := &amp;#34;some string&amp;#34; fmt.Println(&amp;#34;lol&amp;#34;) Go code with triple backtick
a := &amp;quot;some string&amp;quot; fmt.Println(&amp;quot;lol&amp;quot;) JS code with hugo highlight template
const a = &amp;#34;some string&amp;#34; console.log(&amp;#34;lol&amp;#34;) const b = () =&amp;gt; { return 1; }; JS code with triple backtick</description></item></channel></rss>