<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on thecodecousins</title><link>/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on thecodecousins</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 22:00:00 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Using Arduino With PharoThings/Smalltalk</title><link>/posts/using-arduino-with-pharo/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 22:00:00 +0700</pubDate><guid>/posts/using-arduino-with-pharo/</guid><description>Firmata Firmata is a generic protocol for communicating with microcontrollers from software on a host computer. It is intended to work with any host computer software package. Right now there is a matching object in a number of languages. It is easy to add objects for other software to use this protocol. Basically, this firmware establishes a protocol for talking to the Arduino from the host software. The aim is to allow people to completely control the Arduino from software on the host computer.</description></item><item><title>Building my Github Action to deliver doggoes to PRs</title><link>/posts/doggo-action/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 16:08:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/doggo-action/</guid><description>The long awaited GitHub Action feature is finally out of beta and ready to be present in every repositories. GitHub even organized a Hackathon through out March to encourage folks to create more awesome and useful actions. While browsing through the submissions, I found a cool GitHub Action that posts cat gifs on pull requests. Shout out to Ruairidh with his cool idea 👏👏👏.
It&amp;rsquo;ll only do justice to dogs if there&amp;rsquo;s an action that deliver them good boys to our PRs.</description></item><item><title>Git Revert to a Good Commit</title><link>/posts/git-revert-to-a-good-commit/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 14:28:16 +0700</pubDate><guid>/posts/git-revert-to-a-good-commit/</guid><description>Today my co-worker asked me how to revert to an old and good commit on master ( after you accidentally merged dev branch to master ). There are many ways to do that, for example we can use reset to discard all wrong commit to revert back, like undo when writing text. You can find others way onthis topic on Stack Overflow But the problem is too many options, we dont know which one is good, or even dont need to understand - it just works.</description></item><item><title>Host Django Application on AWS</title><link>/posts/host-django-application-on-aws/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 21:30:28 +0800</pubDate><guid>/posts/host-django-application-on-aws/</guid><description>NOTE: This is a cross-posted post from my personal website.
This is an easy and efficient way to get your Django application hosted on AWS for free. I documented these steps while deploying Contikey, an application to share articles between friends.
Note: This is NOT meant for production. Rather it is to quickly host an application on AWS such that it can be accessed without running it on your computer.</description></item><item><title>Quick terminal-based DNS switching</title><link>/posts/dns-command/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2019 14:53:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/dns-command/</guid><description>Motivation Most of us, at some point of our lives, have used at least a custom DNS servers configurations for our computers. Be it for avoiding censorship, faster browsing, security, or bypassing content restriction, we&amp;rsquo;ve all tried setting our DNS servers to some public DNS servers like one from Google (remember 8.8.8.8 and 8.8.4.4?). I myself is also no exception as I have been using 1.1.1.1 for privacy and speed.</description></item><item><title>How I escaped from Microsoft Office tools as a Computer Science student</title><link>/posts/pandoc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 00:35:20 +0700</pubDate><guid>/posts/pandoc/</guid><description>Motivation I have used beamer quite a lot to prepare slides for both research and class presentations. I have started to use LaTeX to content in beamer presentation for two years. Sometimes I was concerned about the high ratio of markup to content in beamer presentations. I used to type thousands lines of code just to create a presentation slide which was tiring and time consuming. Thus, I did some research and found a combination of pandoc, markdown, and LaTeX to simplify my process.</description></item><item><title>Example Blog Post</title><link>/posts/example/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 14:15:59 -0600</pubDate><guid>/posts/example/</guid><description>Section 1 This is some example content
Sub section 1 This is some content for subsection 1
Test Code highlight Go code with hugo highlight template
a := &amp;#34;some string&amp;#34; fmt.Println(&amp;#34;lol&amp;#34;) Go code with triple backtick
a := &amp;quot;some string&amp;quot; fmt.Println(&amp;quot;lol&amp;quot;) JS code with hugo highlight template
const a = &amp;#34;some string&amp;#34; console.log(&amp;#34;lol&amp;#34;) const b = () =&amp;gt; { return 1; }; JS code with triple backtick</description></item></channel></rss>